coupons99.in 2014-12-01

# Privacy Policy | Working Coupons & Deals

**Privacy Policy**

**Q1. When and what kind of details do we amass from our customers?**

Coupons 99 will gather all the essential details only when you will pitch in for our newsletter. Though our website can be visited by you without specifying any details, but if you are placing an order or registering, you would be asked to enter some information like your email address and phone number.

**Q2. For what purpose is the information used?**

All your personal information that is collected by our site, is used in variety of ways:

a)     We use that information to be able to fulfill your requirements in a better manner. We try to improve and personalize your shopping experience.

b)    Information provided by you as well as your feedbacks help us in improving our website for good.

c)     We also try to keep you updated about the new changes in our site by sending mails on regular basis.

d)    The personal information is also used to provide you with details as and when asked by you, and respond to your questions or requirements.

But this doesn’t means that you have cannot leave or unsubscribe from our newsletter. We provide details about the procedure of unsubscribing at the end of emails. So you can follow those instructions and stop receiving emails from us.

**Q3. How do we ensure the safety of information provided by you?**

Your personal information is safe with us and we have adopted a plenty of measures to ensure that each time you enter your personal details in your respective accounts, it stays protected.

  **Q 4. Do we use cookies?**

Yes, we do use cookies. We try our level best to protect your information.

For your information, a cookie is nothing but a small amount of data that is sent for storage in the web browser of user through a website. This happens when the user is still using that particular website. The entire logic of using a cookie is that they can act as a dependable device so as to remember the important information and to keep a record of the browsing activities of the users.

**Q5. Do we reveal your personal information to third party?**

** ** No. Coupon99 doesn’t engage in the selling, trading or in the process of transferring the personal details provided by you. However, we do reveal your details to those who help us in operating our website and contribute in our business. These parties undergo an agreement where they promise to keep your information being provided to them as confidential. Also, we are liable to disclose your information as and when demanded by law, or when it comes to the protection of our rights or for our security or for the enforcement of the policies related to the site. Moreover, for the marketing and advertising purpose we may disclose your non personal information.

**Q6. Do we offer any Third party links?**

**Yes, we do but this happens infrequently. This decision is** totally dependent upon our personal choice. Also, the third parties have their own set of operational policies so we have no interference or responsibility with respect to their activities or any content published by them on our site. Though we do act as a mediator and communicate your feedback about these third party links.

**Q7. Any specific privacy policies for children?**

Coupon99 strictly follows the essentials of children Online Privacy Protection Act. As per that all our products and services are meant for only those who are 13 years or older.

**Q8. Do we store your Browsing details with respect to the site?**

When you use our website you enter into a consent automatically, where you allow us to use your personal details with trusted third parties as specified in detail in the third party link query. You do have an option of opting out of this program and you can do this by clicking on the appropriate option given below.

Opt Out Page.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you give your consent to all the websites privacy policy mentioned above.

**If there are any changes in our privacy policy we would let you know.**
